netblogbox.com 2016-06-30

# Privacy Policy | NetBlog-Box

##  [Privacy Policy](http://www.netblogbox.com/p/privacy-policy.html)

Privacy Policy | NetBlogBox 

## 

 **Last Update :  June 30, 2015 ( <\--- [Download Here PDF](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/google_privacy_policy_en.pdf) \---> )**  
When you demand any more information or get any questions about our privacy policy, make sure you feel free to to contact us simply by E-mail  **[dineshtrick@gmail.com](mailto:dineshtrick@gmail.com)**.

                  In [**Netblog-box**](http://netblogbox.com/), the privacy of our guests/visitors will be associated with intense importance for you to all of us. That privacy policy document outlines the varieties of personal information will be been given in addition to gathered through [**Netblog-box**](http://netblogbox.com/) in addition to just how it's used [applied].

## 

_**Log Files**_

                Just like all kinds of other Websites, **[http://www.NetBlogbox.com/](http://netblogbox.com/)** makes use of Log files. The information Or Details in the Log files involves internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, along with quantity of clicks to analyze movements, administer the website, track user’s movements across the web site, along with collect [gather] demographic details [information]. IP addresses, as well as other this kind of details are not linked with personally identifiable.

## 

_**Cookies and Web Beacon**_

  * [NetBlog-Box](http://netblogbox.com/) does not use cookies.

## 

_**DoubleClick DART Cookie**_

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on **_http://NetBlogBox.com/_**.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to Http://NetBlogBox.com/ and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - ** ** ** _<http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/>_**
  * These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on **[http://www.NetBlogBox.com/](http://netblogbox.com/)** send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.
  * **_http://www.NetBlogBox.com_**  has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
  * You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. **_http://www.NetBlogBox.com/_** privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.
  * If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

## 

_Analytics Of Cookie_

  * Analytics We also use the services of reputable third parties to provide us with data collection, reporting, ad response measurement, and website and mobile application analytics, as well as to assist with delivery of relevant marketing messages and advertisements. These third parties may view, edit or set their own cookies. We, our third party service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies and/or partners may also place web beacons or similar technologies for these third parties. The use of these technologies by these third parties is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by this privacy statement. 
  * An Overview Go To :-   **[The EU Cookie Law](http://www.theeucookielaw.com/)**
